# **Gregory Blood**

Website: gregoryblood.github.io

1115 SW 26th St. Corvallis, Oregon, 97333 (702) 606-7433 gregoryblood1998@gmail.com

#### **Career Objective**

Versatile programmer with experience in both low-level and high-level languages with knowledge in OOP, data structures, and computer networking. I want to combine my creativity with efficiency while working in a team to satisfy given tasks. I believe my attention to detail and analytical thinking will be valuable for your business.

#### **Technical Proficiencies**

#### **Education**

**Oregon State University** - Corvallis, OR (2017-Present)

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

Straight As in all CS courses. Some of these courses include:

# Data Structures – Computer Architecture and Assembly – Web Development – Computer Networking – Software Engineering

### **Experience**

## Data Structure Teacher Assistant - Corvallis, OR (2019-Present)

Working with a professor, I held office hours to help students with data structure concepts, bug-fixing, and best coding practices along with reviewing and grading their projects. I also proctored and graded quizzes for 30+ students.

# Canvassing - Las Vegas, NV (2018-2018)

I chose this job because I wanted to break out of my comfort zone by going door-to-door talking with strangers. Working with a team members, I determined how to efficiently split up territory to talk with diverse people. I learned the value of communicating clearly to figure what information people wanted to know.

#### **Projects**

# My Website - HTML5, CSS3, Javascript - gregoryblood.github.io

To create this site, I thought of it like a sales talk. It had to be enticing to look at, while maintaining quality information. I designed it with a minimalistic style with a limited color palette, with a goal to remove any distractions attract the viewers eyes too clickable links.

# WhatToWear - HTML5, CSS3, Javascript - gregoryblood.github.io/weatherapi

I check the weather every morning to figure out what to wear but don't always know what a number like 54 degrees feels like. So to solve this problem I created a site that uses DarkSky.net's API and the device's location to display as clearly as possible, what kind of clothes to wear and 'weather' you need an umbrella or a raincoat. Some of my friends and I still use this every morning because of the everchanging Oregon weather.

Check out my website for more projects and information